Society of Indian Psychologists; Records apap390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Records from President Gayle S. Morse (Term: 2018-2020)
  - Records for 2011, 1999-2011
    - Cemrrat Grant Proposal, 2011
    - An Historical Profile of American Indians and Alaska Natives in Psychology Presentation, 2011
    - Demographic Chracterisitics of APA Members, 2011
    - Pictures from Joseph Trimble, 2011 January
    - Letter Congratulating The University of North Dakota Chapter, 2011 February 21
    - Letter to Refuse Reimbursement for Joseph Amador, 2012 March 28
    - Letter to NRC in Support of AAPA, 2011 March 3
    - Testimony Before the House Appropriations Subcommittee Interior, Environment, and Related Agencies, 2011 May 3
    - JG Edits of the Meeting Minutes, 2011 June 27
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2011 July 13
    - Letter to the Chair of the DSM-5 Task Force, 2011 July 18
    - SIP Meeting Minutes, 2011 June 27
    - SIP Conference Call Agenda, 2011 August 10
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2011 August 10
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2011 September 14
    - SIP Executive Council Agenda, 2011 October 12
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2011 October 12
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2011 November 9
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2011 December 14
  - Records for 2012
    - Convention Participant List, 2012
    - Indigenous Research Consortium, 2012
    - SIP Membership Description, 2012
    - Leader Development Institte Candidate Rankings, 2012
    - Honoring the Ancestors, Strengthening the Future, 2012
    - Jacqueline Grey, Letter Deferring Jury Duty, 2012
    - Memorandum of Understanding between the APA and SIP, 2012
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2012 January 11
    - Letter from Michelle Johnson-Jennings RE: Mentorship, 2012 January 24
    - Letter from Paula Carter RE: Leader Development Institute, 2012 February 3
    - Letter from Joanna Shadlow RE: Leader Development Institute, 2012 February 6
    - Letter from Wedy Peters RE: Leader Development Institute, 2012 February 6
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2012 February 8
    - Leader Development Institte Congratulations Letter, Dr. Shadlow, 2012 February 17
    - Leader Development Institte Congratulations Letter, Dr. Johnson-Jennings, 2012 February 17
    - Leader Development Institte Congratulations Letter, Dr. Carter, 2012 February 17
    - Leader Development Institte Congratulations Letter, Dr. Peters, 2012 February 17
    - SIP Donation Thank You Letter Template, 2012 February 21
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2012 March 14
    - SIP Executive Council Meeting Minutes, 2012 April
    - Letter RE: Margaret Smith-Zoeller and the Mentoring Program, 2012 October 31
  - Records for 2014, 2013-2014
    - Convention Participation List, 2013
    - General Principles, 2014
    - Commentary on the APA Ehics Code, Introduction, 2014
    - Convention Participant List, 2014
    - Standard 1: Resolving Ethical Issues, 2014
    - Standard 2: Competence, 2014
    - Standard 3: Human Relations, 2014
    - Standard 4: Privacy and Confidentiality, 2014
    - Standard 5: Advertising and Other Public Statements, 2014
    - Standard 6: Record Keeping and Fees, 2014
    - Standard 7: Education and Training, 2014
    - Standard 9: Assessment, 2014
    - Standard 10: Therapy, 2014
    - Values Statement, 2014
    - SIP Commentary on The APA's Ethical Principles of Psychologists and Code of Conduct, 2014
    - NLPA Conference SIP and The Alliance, Presentation, 2014
    - References Sheet, 2014
    - Standard 8: Research and Publication, 2014
    - Commentary on The APA's Ethical Principles of Psychologists and Code of Conduct, Title Page, 2014
    - Violence in the Native American Communities, 2014 May 3
    - SIP By-Laws Update, 2015 May 15
    - Photographs, 2014 June 23
    - Letter RE: Billing for Copies of the SIP Commentary on the APA, 2014 June 26
    - Letter RE: Billing for Copies of the SIP Commentary on the APA, 2014 November 1
  - Records for 2015, 1999-2015
    - Society of Indian Psychologists Statement on Retiring Native American Mascots, 1999; 2015
    - Prioritizing Action Ideas: Verbal instructions, 2015
    - Prioritizing Action Ideas, 2015
    - Prioritizing Action Idea Presentation, 2015
    - SIP Planning Session, 2015
    - Convention Participant List, 2015
    - Call For Nominations NMCS Shining Star Award, 2015
    - Letter From Dr. Subia BigFoot RE: Nomination for Diane Willis for Division 35 Strickland Daniel Mentoring Award, 2015 March 27
    - Letter From Dr. Jane F. Silovsky, RE: Nomination for Diane Willis for Division 35 Strickland Daniel Mentoring Award, 2015 March 27
    - Comment on the January 2015 Cover of the American Psychologist, 2015 April
    - Society of Indian Psychologists Membership List, 2015 June 1
    - Sip Executive Committee Proposed Agenda, 2015 September 11
    - Sip Executive Committee Proposed Agenda, 2015 October 9
    - Sip Executive Committee Proposed Agenda, 2015 November 13
  - Records for 2018, 2016 November 30 - 2018
    - SIP Organization Name Committee Meeting Minutes, 2016 November 30
    - Response and Recommendations Upon Review of the Recent Decision to Set Aside the 2015 ICWA ruling by the 8th Circuit Court of Appeals Letter, 2018
    - SIP Newsletter, Smoke Signals, 2018 January
    - SIP Educational Paper RE: the Use of Counterterrorism Tactics on Native Peoples and Allies, 2018 February 26
    - Letter RE: Iva GreyWolf Nomination National MultiCultural Conference and Summit Distinquished Elder Award, from Gayle Morse, Art Blume, and Jacqueline Gray, 2018 June 1
    - Letter: Nomination of Melinda Garcia, PhD for Distinguished Service Award, from Dr. Wendy Peters, 2018 June 4
    - Letter: Nomination of Melinda Garcia, PhD for Distinguished Service Award, from Dr. Glenna Stumblingbear-Riddle, 2018 June 5
    - Letter: Nomination of Melinda Garcia, PhD for Distinguished Service Award, from Dr. Jacqueline Gray, 2018 June 5
    - Letter of Nomination RE: Art Blume for the 2019 National Multicultural Conference & Summit Distinguished Elder Award, 2018 June 13
    - SIP Organization Name Task Force Report, 2018 June 27
    - Commission on Ethnic Minority Recruitment, Retention, and Training in Psychology II (CEMRRAT2) Task Force Decision Letter, 2018 September 6
    - Division 35, Section 6 Awards, 2018
    - Iva GreyWolf Biography, 2018
    - Honoring the Ancestors, 2018
  - Records for 2019, 2016 July 1 - 2019
    - Midwinter Meeting Agenda, 2019 February 15
    - Letter for Division 45 Cosponsorship of SIP Conference Speaker, 2010 March 1
    - Interest Survey, All Responses, 2019 March 13
    - SIP Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, with Gayle Notes, 2019 March 15
    - SIP Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2019 March 15
    - SIP Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2019 April 19
    - SIP Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 2019 April 19
    - Letter to the Coalition for the Advancement & Application of Psychological Science (CAAPS), 2019 April 20
    - SIP Response to CAAPS invitation, 2019 April 21
    - SIP Statement RE: Wearing Regalia at Graduation, 2019 April 22
    - Letter to Cerynn RE: Permission to Recruit and Interview Participants for Dissertation at SIP Conference, 2019 April 23
    - Letter to Amanda Young RE: Webinar Presentation, 2019 May 30
    - SIP Executive Committee List, 2019 June
    - Letter RE: SIP Executive Committee Decision to Remove Damian Vraniak, 2019 June 5
    - Letter to Mark Baez RE: Request to conduct Survey with SIP Members, 2019 June 21
    - Business Meeting Agenda, 2019 June 24
    - SIP Annual Convention Meeting Minutes, 2019 June 24
    - 32nd Annual Convention American Indian Psychology and Psychology Graduate Students, Program, 2019 June 24; 2019 June 25
    - SIP Presidential Trio Meeting Minutes, 2019 June 29
    - SIP Final Financial Yearly Report, 2016 July 1; 2017 June 30
    - SIP Executive Committee Vote of Membership Removal of Damian Vraniak, 2019 July 7
    - Smoke Signals Newsletter, 2019 August; 2019 September
    - SIP Mentorship Chair Report, 2017 October 25
    - SIP Mentorship Committee Budget Proposal, 2017 December 12
    - Clayton Logan, brief biography, 2019
    - Nicole Thompson, brief biography, 2019
    - 32nd Annual Convention American Indian Psychology and Psychology Graduate Students, Agreement, 2019
    - Report from Art Blume, Winter Meeting 2019
    - SIP Budget, 2019
    - SIP Budget, 2020
    - Smoke Signals Newsletter, Mentorship Special Edition, 2019
    - The Color of Justice, The Landscape of Traumatic Justice: Youth of Color in Conflict with the Law, Publication, 2019
    - SIP Stephen C. Rose Scholarship for Psychology Research on American Indian, Alaska Native, and Native Hawaiian Youth Application, 2019
    - Letter from NMCSCalling for Nominations for the NMCS Lifetime Achievement Community Engagement Award, 2019
    - National Multicultural Conference and Summit - Elders Nomination Form, Jacqueline Gray, 2019
    - National Multicultural Conference and Summit - Elders Nomination Form, Teresa LaFromboise, 2019
    - Call for Nominations NMCS Rising Star Award Early Career, 2019